<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="tnc.xsl"?>

<catalog>
  <cd>
    <title><b>Acceptance of Terms</b></title>
    <artist>The XYZ.com website ("Website") is an internet based entertainment ticketing portal owned and operated by Bigtree Entertainment Private Limited ("Bigtree"), a company incorporated under the laws of India, with its registered office at Gr. Floor, Wajeda House, Gulmohar Cross 7. Juhu Scheme, Mumbai 400049.
Through the Website, Bigtree shall provide you ("User") entertainment-related information, pricing, availability and reservations for ticket for cinemas, plays, concerts, sports events across cities and rural areas throughout India ("Service"), as more particularly described and defined in the terms of service ("TOS") relating to such Service, This Service may be availed by the User, his family members</artist>
    </cd>
<cd>
	<title>Privacy Policy </title>
   	<artist>The User hereby consents, expresses and agrees that he has read and fully understands the Privacy Policy of Bigtree in respect of the Website, The User further consents that the terms and contents of such Privacy Policy are acceptable to him.

		Any customer grievances can be reported to the Grievance Officer specifically dedicated to address all customer concerns.</artist>
</cd>
<cd>
	<title>User's Obligations and User Account </title>
   	<artist>In consideration of use of the Website, the User represent and confirm that the User is of legal age to enter into a binding contract and is not a person barred from using the Website and/or receiving the Services under the laws of India or other applicable law.
To avail a Service the User has and must continue to maintain at his sole cost: (a) all the necessary equipments including a computer and modem etc. to access the Website/avail Services; (b) own access to the World Wide Web. The User shall be responsible for accessing the Services and that access may involve third party fees including, airtime charges or internet service provider?s charges which are to be exclusively borne by the User.
The user also understands that the services may include certain communications from Bigtree as service announcements and administrative messages. the user understands and agrees that the services are provided on an "as is" basis and that Bigtree does not assume any responsibility for deletions, mis-delivery or failure to store any user communications or personalized settings. </artist>
</cd>

<cd>
	<title>Limited User </title>
   	<artist> The User agrees and undertakes not to sell, trade or resell or exploit for any commercial purposes, any portion of the Service. For the removal of doubt, it is clarified that the Website is not for commercial use but is specifically meant for personal use only.

The User further agrees and undertakes not to reverse engineer, modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, software, products or services obtained from the Website. For the removal of doubt, it is clarified that unlimited or wholesale reproduction, copying of the content for commercial or non-commercial purposes and unwarranted modification of data and information within the content of the Website is not permitted.  </artist>
</cd>

<cd>
	<title>Prohibition Against Unlawful Use </title>
   	<artist> As a condition of the use of the Website, the User warrants that they will not use the Website for any purpose that is unlawful or illegal under any law for the time being in force within or outside India or prohibited by this Agreement and/or the TOS including both specific and implied. In addition, the Website shall not be used in any manner, which could damage, disable, overburden or impair it or interfere with any other party's use and/or enjoyment of the Website. The User shall refrain from obtaining or attempting to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for or through the Website.  </artist>
</cd>
	
  
</catalog> 
